Ah
Nangang project supplier pre-communication approval
Approver Fu Wenyao
Wenyao
The problem is
the Fu family just confirmed Fu Chenzhou's identity
and the branch family immediately pushes this project
If he agrees today
if anything goes wrong with the project later
he will take all the blame
Mrs Fu
Are you implying I should
shift the project risks to Chenzhou
I'm not implying anything
I only read what's written in the document
One more thing
Before the Nangang project audit is completed
do not use my name to publicly
release any signals of progress
Mr Fu, you've worked hard early on
Since you're in charge of pushing the project
please cooperate and explain things during the audit
That's settled